var questions = [{
	"question": "A collection of related data?",
	"option1":"Information",
	"option2":"Valuable information",
	"option3":"Database",
	"option4":"Metadata",
	"answer":"3"
}, {
	"question":"DBMS manages the interation between ______ and database?",
	"option1":"users",
	"option2":"End users",
	"option3":"Clients",
	"option4":"Stake Holders",
	"answer":"2"
}, {
	"question":"Object= ______ + relationship?",
	"option1":"data",
	"option2":"attributes",
	"option3":"Constraints",
	"option4":"Entity",
	"answer":"4"
}, {
	"question":"A characteristics of Entity?",
	"option1":"Relation",
	"option2":"Attribute",
	"option3":"Parameter",
	"option4":"Constraints",
	"answer":"2"
} , {
	"question":"Which one of the following not done by data Link Layer ?",
	"option1":"Framing",
	"option2":"Flow control",
	"option3":"channel coding",
	"option4":"Error control",
	"answer":"3"
} , {
	"question":"Physical or Logical arrangement of Network?",
	"option1":"Topology",
	"option2":"Routing",
	"option3":"Networking",
	"option4":"None of the above",
	"answer":"1" 
},{
	"question":"Expand WAN?",
	"option1":"World area network",
	"option2":"wide area network",
	"option3":"web area network",
	"option4":"None of the above",
	"answer":"2"  
} ,{
	"question":"If a process fails,most operating system write the error information to a ___?",
	"option1":"log file",
	"option2":"Another Running process",
	"option3":"new file",
	"option4":"none of the above",
	"answer":"1" 
		 
} ,{
	"question":"Which one of the following can not be scheduled by the kernel?",
	"option1":"kernel level thread",
	"option2":"user level thread",
	"option3":"process",
	"option4":"None of the above",
	"answer":"2" 
		 
}, {
	"question":"which one of the following is the deadlock avoidance algorithm?",
	"option1":"Round robin algorithm",
	"option2":"banker's algorithm",
	"option3":"elevator algorithm",
	"option4":"karn's algorithm",
	"answer":"2" 		 
}];
